<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Janus Valberg-Madsen</title>
    <link>https://janusvm.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Janus Valberg-Madsen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://janusvm.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding dependencies on the fly in a Makefile</title>
      <link>https://janusvm.github.io/2018/10/27/adding-dependencies-on-the-fly-in-a-makefile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janusvm.github.io/2018/10/27/adding-dependencies-on-the-fly-in-a-makefile/</guid>
      <description>Imagine the following situation:
You have a bunch of files that are being built by the same rule in a Makefile, but some of them further depend on some other input files. It&amp;rsquo;s far from the most of the targets that have these dependences, and those that do depend on different subsets of the extra dependences. How should the Makefile for this look?
I found myself in this very situation not long ago, when I was working on the slides for my Git Workshop, which included a lot of SVG figures depicting commit graphs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World! (2)</title>
      <link>https://janusvm.github.io/2018/10/25/hello-world-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janusvm.github.io/2018/10/25/hello-world-2/</guid>
      <description>Second time&amp;rsquo;s the charm, right?
Last time I made an attempt at getting my github.io site up and running, it ended up being half-baked and I left it unused for over a year. In the meantime, my number of repositories with GitHub Pages steadily increased, resulting in a bunch of janusvm.github.io/repo links that were nowhere to be found on what ought to be the root site.
After giving three talks this month, each with slides on GH Pages, I decided it was time to organise my stuff and update this website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>